ie.edu 2017-08-07

# Schools | IE - Reinventing Higher Education

This Privacy Policy sets out the bases pursuant to which Instituto de Empresa, S.L., with registered office at C/ María de Molina 13, Madrid (Spain), and with Tax Code (NIF) B-82334319 or the entities listed below when visiting the websites operated by them (“IE” or the “Controller”), processes your personal data when you provide when visiting the https:www.ie.edu website, or when using the mobile app or other applications, software, digital media, programmes or devices that are authorised to interact and use other functionalities relating to the same:

<http://www.ie.edu/es/universidad/> \- IE Universidad, NIF G40155384, with registered office in Segovia, C/ Cardenal Zuñiga, 12, and recognized as a private University in virtue of Law 4/1997, of abril 24, published in the Official Diary of Castilla y León on April 30th, 1997 and at B.O.E. in July 1st, 1997.

<http://www.ie.edu/es/ie-foundation/> \- Fundación IE, NIF G81711459, with registered office in Madrid, C/ María de Molina, 13, and duly registered in the Foundations Registry with number 28-1053.

<http://www.ie.edu/es/alumni/> \- Asociación de Antiguos Alumnos del Instituto de Empresa, NIF G78284528, and registered office in Madrid, C/ María de Molina, 13.

[https://store.ie.edu/ ](https://store.ie.edu/)\- Editorial Instituto de Empresa, S.L., NIF B79192530, with registered office in Madrid, C/ María de Molina, 13.

Therefore, you may enter web sites operated by the abovementioned service providers when visiting this website, all of them severally considered Data Controllers with respect to the data provided in their corresponding websites. All these websites shall be jointly referred as the “Website”.

Each time that you visit the Website and provide us with, or we are required to have access to, any kind of information that, given its characteristics, allows us to identify you (the “Personal Data”), this shall be governed by the contents of the Spanish Data Protection Act (the “LOPD”) and its implementing regulations, this present Privacy Policy, the General Terms and Conditions for Use of the Website (the “Legal Notice”) and any other documents relating thereto (jointly referred to herein as the “Terms and Conditions”) that may apply from time to time, and you must read these documents in order to confirm that you agree with their contents.

Our Terms and Conditions may be modified, and we therefore recommend that you read them regularly.

#### 1\. GATHERING OF PERSONAL DATA AND THE REASONS FOR ITS PROCESSING

Please remember that before making use of any of our services or functionalities you must read this Privacy Policy.

If you fail to provide certain information that is classified as compulsory, this may mean that it is not possible to manage your registration as a user or permit the use of certain functionalities or services offered via the Website.

The user guarantees that the Personal Data provided is true and accurate and undertakes to give notice of any change or modification to such data, assuming liability for any loss or damage caused to the Website, IE or any third party as the result of the provision of erroneous, inaccurate or incomplete data. In the event that you provide Personal Data belonging to third parties, you are responsible for informing them and obtaining their consent for the provision of such data for the purposes indicated in the relevant sections of this Privacy Policy.

Your personal data will be incorporated into a file owned by INSTITUTO DE EMPRESA, S.L. or, as the case may be, the service providers listed above, with the aim of rendering services requested and for which you have been expressly registered. Your personal data may be also used for providing information regarding their activities, developing profiles, making statistics or market research, quality surveys and eventually improving the interaction with you.

You expressly consent that communications about our relationship could be made by electronic means.

#### 2\. SUBSCRIPTION TO THE NEWSLETTER

In the event that you authorise your subscription to IE Newsletters, we will send you personalised information and promotional material relating to the products and services offered by IE Group in general, which may include commercial communications by any proprietary or third party means.

In order to enhance the service that we offer you, we hereby inform you that the Personal Data relating to your purchases from our on-line and physical stores, along with your tastes and preferences, may be used for the purpose of analysis, the creation of user profiles, marketing studies, quality surveys and the improvement of interaction with our customers.

You may cancel your subscription via the Newsletter section of the Website at any time. 

#### 3\. DATA PROTECTION RIGHTS

The data controllers hereby undertake to respect the confidentiality of your Personal Data and to guarantee the exercise of your rights. You may exercise your rights of access, correction, cancellation and objection at any time by sending an email to soportededatos@ie.edu, giving the reason for your request. 

#### 4\. OTHER NECESSARY USES OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA 

In order to comply with the stated aims of this Privacy Policy, we may be required to disclose or forward your personal data to other organisations belonging to the IE Group, and we therefore understand that in registering and providing us with information via the Website, you expressly authorise us to disclose and/or forward your data in this way.

It may also be necessary to forward your Personal Data to third parties that provide us with support services, in their capacity as data processors. In providing us with your Personal Data via this Website, you hereby expressly authorise us to process and share your data with the said collaborating parties, which may be located in places that do not offer a level of protection that is comparable to that offered within the European Economic Area.
